<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kamhome Pharmacy</string>

    <string name="open_menu">open</string>
    <string name="close_menu">close</string>
    <string name="cortem1">A thin wrapper around a millisecond value that allows JDBC to identify this as an SQL DATE
        value. A milliseconds value represents the number of milliseconds that have passed since January 1, 1970 00:00:00.000 GMT.
        To conform with the definition of SQL DATE.
        </string>
    <string name="covidex">A RatingBar is an extension of SeekBar and ProgressBar that shows a rating in stars.
        The user can touch/drag or use arrow keys to set the rating when using the default size RatingBar.
        The smaller RatingBar style</string>
    <string name="duocotexin">A TextView displays text to the user and optionally allows them to edit it.
        A TextView is a complete text editor, however the basic class is configured to not allow editing.
        </string>
    <string name="mebendazole">The Android framework includes support for various cameras and camera features
        available on devices, allowing you to capture pictures and videos in your applications.
        This document discusses a quick, simple approach to image and video capture and outlines an advanced
        approach for creating custom camera experiences for your users.</string>
    <string name="panadol1">RecyclerView is the ViewGroup that contains the views corresponding to your data.
        Its a view itself so you add RecyclerView into your layout the way you would add any other UI element.
        Each individual element in the list is defined by a view holder object.
    </string>
    <string name="piliton">A TextView displays text to the user and optionally allows them to edit it.
        A TextView is a complete text editor, however the basic class is configured to not allow editing.
    </string>
    <string name="probeta">A TextView displays text to the user and optionally allows them to edit it.
        A TextView is a complete text editor, however the basic class is configured to not allow editing.
    </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


</resources>